http://www.rachelcobbsoprano.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYThe privacy of your information is important to us. Through the operation of this website, we will collect information about you. We want you to understand what information is being collected and why. Please find this privacy policy as an explanation. This privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check it often.Anonymous InformationWeebly may collect certain technical and routing information about your computer, which is automatically submitted to us by your browser and does not personally identify you. This information may include browser type, operating system and CPU speed, your IP address, and search requests and results. The only information Rachel Cobb Vocal Studios collects is your email and name information if you choose to contact us. We hate spammers and would never sell anything of yours.CookiesThis site is run by Weebly and uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that assign you a unique identifier. The collection of this information permits us to administer our site more efficiently and to provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. You may set your browser to prevent cookies from being sent; if you do so, this may limit the functionality of our site.Third Party LinksThird parties that link on this site may use cookies or collect other information when you go to their site. We do not control the collection or use of your information by these companies. You should contact these companies directly if you have any questions about their collection or use of information about you. Luckily there are no third parties on this site, but for legal reasons I am including this sentence.Personally Identifiable InformationThe only personally identifiable information we collect is that which you voluntarily provide. We will use this information in order to send you emails regarding offers, products, and services we think may interest you. We may also use it to conduct marketing research, and improve our products and services. When you submit personally identifiable information to us, you understand that you are agreeing to allow us to access, store, and use it for those purposes.We may share this information with third parties, but only those parties we trust to help us run our website and online business, and who agree to keep your information confidential. We may also provide this information if requested by law enforcement upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. Financial InformationThrough this website we DO NOT sell products and services. But if we decide to, and forget to update this page, you should know that In order to purchase our products and services you will be asked to provide financial information. Typically this information will be collected by a third-party provider. In the event that the information is collected by us, we will not disclose your financial information to anyone unless required to do so by court order. Opt-Out PolicyIf at any time you do not wish to receive offers and e-mails from us, we ask that you tell us. There will be instructions to opt-out of our mailing list on the emails you receive from us. Note: I don't send newsletters :)SecurityWe take measures to maintain the security of the personal information you have provided to us.  Even so, we cannot guarantee that all information shared through the internet will remain secure and you agree that we are not responsible for any unauthorized, inadvertent disclosure. Children’s Privacy This site is not meant for children under the age of 18 years old.  We do not knowingly collect information pertaining to or market to children under the age of 18 years old.Transfer of Customer InformationCompany customer lists and information are considered business assets and as such, in the event that we merge with another entity or if we sell our assets to another entity, our business assets, including our customer lists and information, would be transferred to that entity.CONTACT: Should you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Updated: December 2019
Proudly powered by Weebly
Home
Sound Healing
Lessons
Biography
Resume
Video
Photos
